

ABOUT ME

Computer Engineer by training, he is creative, committed and with high attention to detail. He has about 3 years of experience in software development, such as web development and UI/UX fundamentals. He has recently received awards in the company where he is currently working, for his work attitude, work results and innovation in software solutions. He has an advanced level of English, and he is certified in SCRUM and agile methods.

CONTACT

Phone: +57 (300)-3805184 Email: santiriva19@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://santiagorivadeneira.com

Linkedin: Visit my profile

EDUCATION

Universidad de la Sabana

Informatics Engineer, 2018/1 - Present

- Member of the football team and represents the university in regional championships.
- · Certified in scrum and agile methods

Colegio Para Hijos de empleados de la Contraloría General de la República

High-school, 2017

- · Graduado con honores académicos
- Vicepresidente del Club de Matemática, 2012

SANTIAGO RIVADENEIRA DEGLADO

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

WORK HISTORY

Full-stack developer

Howdy, Dec 2021 - Present

- He currently uses mainly Javascript for developing web pages, using the framework React Js for the frontend and Node JS for the backend.
- He participates in all the SCRUM events of the development team.
- He is a part of a development team conformed by around 80 developers around the globe.
- He currently combines his work responsibilities with his university and with the soccer practices. Which has gave him even more discipline than before.
- He has been developing a chrome extension to scrap information from Google Flights website.

Software Developer

Teleperformance SAS, Nov 2020 - Dec 2021

- He used Javascript for developing web pages, using the framework React Js for the frontend and Node JS for the backend.
- He was hired to use RPA (Robot Process Automation)
- He was also the main designer and frontend developer of the development team.

Fullstack Developer

Consorcio Delgado Murcia, Jun 2020 - Nov 2020

- Built, developed and implemented a web page responsive and fully informative.
- Responsible of developing the designing the product (frontend) using mockup tools such as Photoshop and Adobe XD.

Alonzo And Tracy Mourning (Miami)

High-school, 2015

• Attended 9th grade in Miami to learn english.

Norman S. Edelpcurp (Miami)

Middle-school, 2013

· Attended 6th grade in Miami to learn english

Frontend developer

Terra Engineering, Jan 2020 - Jun 2020

- Built, developed and implemented a web page responsive and fully informative.
- Responsible of developing the designing the product (frontend) using mockup tools such as Photoshop and Adobe XD.

HTML React JS Node.js NextJs Vanilla JS Chrome Ext Git CI/CD Vercel RPA Java CSS

SQL Server

RELEVANT COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

MySQL

Curso de Webpack

Platzi, sept 2022

SASS

Curso de Desarrollo de Apps para iOS

Figma

Platzi, jun 2022

Curso Básico de GraphQL

Platzi, dec 2021

Unit Testing con Jest en React

Platzi, Dec 2021

Node.js: Base de Datos con MongoDB y WebSockets

Platzi, Nov 2021

Scrum Foundations Professional Certificate

Udemy, Juli 2021

MongoDB

Automation Anywhere Foundations

Udemy, Nov 2020

React Native Complete Course

Udemy, Nov 2020

Agile Methods Concepts

University of La Sabana, May 2020

Introduction to IoT

Cisco, May 2022